export const quiz = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'What is the most common version control system used by software teams to manage changes to source code over time?',
    answers: ['SQL', 'Git', 'Notepad', 'Email'],
    answer: 'Git'
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'What Git command is the opposite of and to undo the git add index.html command?',
    answers: ['git reset index.html', 'git remove index.html', 'git remote index.html', 'git repack index.html'],
    answer: 'git reset index.html'
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'What is the latest version of Hypertext Markup Language (HTML)?',
    answers: [3, 4, 5, 6],
    answer: 5
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'What does Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) not allow you to control?',
    answers: ['color', 'font', 'decorations', 'structure'],
    answer: 'structure'
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'What is another name for the conditional operator in JavaScript as a one line if-else expression?',
    answers: ['Trinary', 'Ternary', 'Trenery', 'Truancy'],
    answer: 'Ternary'
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'What is the best part of Enspiral Dev Academy (EDA)?',
    answers: ['the team', 'the meditation', 'mental muscle memory', 'all of the above'],
    answer: 'all of the above'
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'What placeholder would you use for a Handlebars template ?',
    answers: ['{{{body}}}', 'mustache', '{}', 'layout'],
    answer: '{{{body}}}'
  },

  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'Which of these is not a Knex.js join method?',
    answers: ['innerJoin', 'crossJoin', 'leftJoin', 'overJoin'],
    answer: 'overJoin'
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'What is not normally included in the Test Driven Development (TDD) approach?',
    answers: ['green', 'red', 'refactor', 'rewire'],
    answer: 'rewire'
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'In React.js, what is the shorthand syntax for <React.Fragment></React.Fragment>?',
    answers: ['<div></div>', '<></>', '<>', '{}'],
    answer: '<></>'
  }
]
